edu.com 2005-06-05

# Student Advantage Discount Card: Privacy Policy

This website and the Student Advantage Discount Card are part of the Student Advantage Network (the "Network"), which is owned and/or operated by Student Advantage, Inc. ("Student Advantage"). This privacy statement has been created in order to disseminate our firm commitment to the privacy of our Cardholders . The following statement discloses our information-gathering and dissemination practices on studentadvantage.com and for the Student Advantage Cardholders and across the Network of which these two services are a part. 

The Network collects information in order to serve our program cardholders and online users better. This information allows the Network to provide better information and services, including discounts and commerce opportunities for our cardholder programs, and to create a valuable community in which to discuss thoughts, issues and experiences. Student Advantage, Inc. and its affiliates will use the information we collect to provide you with valuable services, and we will not sell your information to other companies without your consent.

Table of Contents  
  
1\. The Information We Gather  
2\. How We Use and Disclose Your Information  
3\. Choice/Opt-out  
4\. Improper Conduct  
5\. Security   
6\. Protection for Children  
7\. Your Consent  
8\. Contacting Us  

1\. The Information We Gather.  

* * *

Registration Information -- To process your application for a Student Advantage Card, or to register your Student Advantage Card online, we require users to give us contact information (like their name, street address and e-mail address), demographic information (like their state, zip code, birth date, gender, university and enrollment status), and payment information (a credit card). We may share certain of your information with third parties who issue or manufacture the Student Advantage cards. We also use your information to send you information about our company and promotional material on behalf of our partners, to notify winners of sweepstakes or contests, and to contact you when necessary. You may opt out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Transaction Information - We may continually gather data concerning your transactions with us, our partners or others. This information may include your Student Advantage Card usage and other information. We use this data to provide you with better information, discounts and other offerings across our Network and from third parties.

Surveys -- Surveys on our Network ask visitors for contact information (like their e-mail address). We use contact data from our surveys to send users confirmation of having successfully submitted the survey, information about our company and promotional material on behalf of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Contests/Promotions -- We run contests on our Network in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their e-mail address). We use contact data from our contests to send users confirmation of having successfully entered the contest, to notify the winners of contests, information about our company and promotional material on behalf of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

Co-branded Cardholder Applications and Offers -- In order to receive special offers from certain of our partners that are identified by name ("Co-Branded Partners"), you may be asked to provide additional personally identifiable information. Information submitted in conjunction with an offer made by a Co-Branded Partner may be shared with the Co-Branded Partner, in which case the Co-Branded Partners' use of such information will be governed by the privacy policy of that particular Co-Branded Partner. Check the Co-Branded Partner's site for specifics.

Prospect Information -- Our Network also collects prospect information from our users. Our users may provide another person's information, such as their friend's e-mail address, in order to send them content or offerings from our Network. The prospect's information is only used for the purpose for which it was submitted. This prospect information will never be shared with third party advertisers. We will never sell or release the prospect information to anyone, except when required by law. Prospects may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

IP Address - Sites on our Network may track your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. 

Cookies -- Sites on our Network use "cookies" (a small data file that's stored on your hard drive) to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit. We do not use cookies to retrieve personal information from your computer. The cookie we give you stores your user id and tells us whether you've logged in or not. We need to know who you are so we can do things like show you your personal e-mail instead of showing you somebody else's. If you have your browser set to not accept cookies, then you won't be able to log into parts of the Network or access most of our products. We may also use cookies to track the performance of promotions and offerings on websites on our Network.

At times, some of the advertisers on our Network set cookies when you select their advertising banner or other forms of advertising. While we use cookies in other parts of our Network (as noted above), any information collected by cookies received with banner ads are collected by those advertisers (or their third-party ad serving company or other agents), and we do not always have access to that information. The advertiser's (and/or its third-party ad serving company's or other agent's) privacy policy will govern the use of this information, and Student Advantage is not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties. 

'Powered By' Content - Sites on the Network provide content that is 'powered by', 'provided by' and co-branded with other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. As a general rule you should always look for and review a site's privacy policy before giving out any personal information. 

External Links -- Sites on our Network contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. As a general rule you should always look for and review a site's privacy policy before giving out any personal information.  
  
back to top  

2\. How We Use and Disclose Your Information  

* * *

We use your information to deliver personalized services, content, discounts and advertisements to enhance your experience with us. For example, we may send you an e-mail with a special offer or discount from one of our affiliates, divisions or participating sponsors on Spring Break travel because you selected "travel" as an area of interest under your personal profile when you registered to use a site on the Network.

We do not sell your personally identifiable information to third parties or mass marketers without your consent. For example, we will not sell another company your name or e-mail address without your consent. Unless you consent to the disclosure of your personally identifiable information, only we and our affiliates, our technical consultants, third party auditors and other third parties who make our site available, enhance its functionality, or provide associated services and/or who deal with you in delivering content, samples, products, and gifts and prizes, have access to this information, and we require them to agree that they are covered by this policy. Please note that we do reserve the right to transfer your personally identifiable information and other information to our successors in business and purchasers of site assets.

On occasion, we may ask for your consent to share particular data with a third party. In addition, we reserve the right, without disclosing your personally identifiable information to third parties, to use the information you provide to offer you additional Student Advantage or third party products and services that we think will be of interest to you. If you respond to such an offer and contact a third party, that third party's privacy policy will apply to any information you provide and/or that is collected by such third party. Similarly, as noted above, information submitted in conjunction with an offer made by a Co-Branded Partner may be shared with the Co-Branded Partner, in which case the Co-Branded Partners' use of such information will be governed by the privacy policy of that particular Co-Branded Partner.

We also do disclose aggregated data to our advertisers and Co-Branded Partners and other third parties to generate reports, marketing and technical research and for related business purposes. For example, we tell advertisers how many people saw or clicked on an ad and additionally, how many people saw or clicked on ads in different portions of our service. Where available, we may offer additional information about viewer characteristics. However, this does not include personally identifiable information about you or your online usage patterns. Our advertisers allow us to provide our service to you. In return, they need to know how to effectively place their ads to potential customers.

You have the option to subscribe to receive various e-mail mail and/or mobile phone updates when you register on certain sites on our Network. We will use these updates to provide you with additional discounts, special offers, site upgrades, new features, events, promotions, and much more. You have the option to opt out of receiving mobile phone communications by e-mailing Card Services or changing the preferences on your account.

On occasion, Student Advantage may use content you post in chat rooms and discussions or any other public section of the Network for promotional purposes, in e-mail newsletters, in promotional collateral, or elsewhere, both on its own and aggregated with any other information you provide through the Network, and by using any site in our Network you agree that we may do so. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these areas, since anyone - not just Student Advantage - may use publicly posted information. (You may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.)

We participate in programs where certain companies ("Participating Companies") direct users to our Network or provide certain incentives or benefits to our users. If you are directed to a service in our Network by such a program (a "Participating Company Program") and you provide or we collect personally identifiable information or non-personally identifiable information in connection with the Participating Company Program, we may share this information with other parties that are participants in the Participating Company Program or that administer the Participating Company Program. For example, if you come to a site on our Network as a referral from an online affiliate program, we may have a contractual obligation to make payments to and send certain corresponding information to the affiliate site that linked you to us and to a separate entity, if any, that administers the affiliate program. Similarly, when you use your Student Advantage card at any merchant or sponsor, we may provide any or all of your information to that merchant or sponsor.

Information obtained in connection with any service on the Network may be intermingled with and used by us in conjunction with information obtained through sources other than that service, including both offline and online sources, both on and off the Network.  
  
back to top  

3\. Choice/Opt-out  

* * *

You have the option to sign up for free e-mail updates and/or mobile phone messages when you apply for a Student Advantage Card. You will also have the option to opt out of receiving the updates. The e-mail opt-out messaging will appear at the bottom of every e-mail that is sent out to mobile phone opt-outs requests should be sent to Card Services via e-mail. You can also opt-out of both email and mobile phone communications by changing your account preferences online.  
  
back to top  

4\. Improper Conduct  

* * *

The restrictions above will not apply in the event that you engage in certain improper conduct. Specifically, Student Advantage shall have the right to itself use or release to third parties personally identifiable information regarding users who are suspected of having used this web site or any other service in the Network for any fraudulent purposes or having otherwise violated any law, rule or regulation or the rights of third parties or having engaged in any conduct which Student Advantage deems improper. By using any service in the Network, you are agreeing to our use or release of any information you provide in any manner we deem appropriate or necessary if you are suspected of having engaged in any conduct which Student Advantage deems improper.  
  
back to top  

5\. Security  

* * *

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. We make a diligent effort to ensure that our secure server software (SSL) is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. Our SSL encrypts all of your personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, to protect the information as it travels over the Internet. We also take contractual, administrative and physical steps to protect against unauthorized access to and disclosure of individually identifiable information. If, during their employment, Student Advantage employees acquire confidential or proprietary information belonging to Student Advantage or its users, such information will be handled in confidence and may not be disclosed to unauthorized third parties. Please note, however, that no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. As a result, we cannot guarantee the security of the information that you transmit via our online services.  
  
back to top  

6\. Protection for Children  
We have no intention of collecting personally identifiable information from children (i.e., individuals under the age of 13). Where appropriate, we take reasonable measures to inform children not to submit such information to our site or in response to advertisements. If a child has provided us with personally identifiable information, that child's parent or guardian should contact our Customer Service Department at info@studentadvantage.com, or via mail to SA Card Services, 280 Summer Street, Boston, MA 02210 if they would like the information submitted by the child deleted from our database. We will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.  
  
back to top  

7\. Your Consent  

* * *

By using any web site or other service in the Network, you consent to the collection, use, and storage of your personal and non-personal information as described above. You also authorize the export of personal information and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us. Our headquarters are located in the USA in Boston, Massachusetts. This policy and our legal obligations are subject to the laws of Massachusetts and the USA, regardless of the location of any user. Any claims or complaints must be filed in the USA in the State of Massachusetts. 

We may amend our Privacy Policy, but if we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, so you can always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. Any changes will only apply to information collected after the change is posted.  
  
back to top  

8\. Contacting Us  

* * *

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of the Network, or your dealings with the Network, you can e-mail us at [info@studentadv antage.com](mailto:info@studentadvantage.com), or send mail to us at SA Card Services, 280 Summer Street, Boston, MA 02210.  
In addition, if you have any questions about the Student Advantage site or Student Advantage Card you can e-mail us at [info@studentadvantage.com](mailto:info@studentadvantage.com), or send us mail at SA Card Services, 280 Summer Street, Boston, MA 02210 .  
  
back to top  
  
|
